It is a lovely sunny morning.
Ah! What a nice day for doing nothing!
Daddy pig loves doing nothing.
Daddy, aren¡¯t you going to work today?
No, Peppa, it¡¯s Saturday.
Daddy pig doesn¡¯t work on Saturdays.
Daddy pig, you¡¯ll be late for work!
But it is Saturday, mummy pig, isn¡¯t it?
No. It¡¯s Thursday!
Oh!
Daddy pig works on Thursdays.
See you later.
Bye bye.
Poor daddy, having to work! Lucky
mummy, you can play at home all day.
I¡¯m not playing.
I¡¯m working on my computer.
George wants to play
the Happy Mrs. Chicken game.
George, we can play the Happy
Mrs.chicken game after I finish my work.
Oh.
Mummy sheep and Suzy have
come to pick up Peppa for playgroup.
Hello Peppa!
Hello Suzy!
Have a good day at the play group.
Bye bye mummy. Work hard¡­
Mrs. Sheep,
do you work or do you play?
I¡¯m going to be working very
hard today¡­I¡¯m off to the gym.
What do you do at the gym?
Running, jumping and skipping.
Mummy, that¡¯s not work. That¡¯s play.
Peppa and Suzy have
arrived at the play group.
Hello everyone!
Hello Peppa, hello Suzy!
Ah ho, Children!
Today,we would play shops!
Woo!
Who wants to be shopkeeper?
Me, me, me!
Peppa and Suzy can be shopkeepers.
Everyone else can be customers.
Peppa and Suzy are
going to run a pretend shop.
What do we have to do?
I¡¯ll take the money Suzy
and you can start the shelves.
OK.
Danny dog is the first customer.
Hello shopkeeper.
Hello Mr. Dog.
Can I have some biscuits please?
Suzy, have we got any biscuits?
No, but we¡¯ve got a toy telephone.
How much will that be?
That will be a hundred pounds please¡­
Thank you. Next please.
Hello shopkeeper, can I
have a loaf of bread please?
No, but you can have a toy house.
Would you like it in a bag, sir?
Yes, please.
That will be one of penny please.
Oh, I haven¡¯t got enough money.
You can pay us next time
you come in. Gosh! This is hard work.
Yes!
Hello shopkeeper! What can I buy for
a million thousand pounds please?
Suzy, what have we got
for a million thousand pounds?
Em¡­a carrot.
Yes, please.
Rebecca Rabbit likes carrots.
It is home time.
Daddy pig has
come to collect Peppa and Suzy.
Daddy, have you had a busy day?
Yes, I¡¯ve been working very hard.
We¡¯ve been working very hard too.
We¡¯ve been shopkeepers.
Blah, blah,blah, .....The end and print.
Mummy pig has finished her works.
Ok George, perhaps we can just
play one game of Happy Mrs. Chicken.
We¡¯ve earned it.
Naughty mummy! You
are playing Happy Mrs. Chicken.
Ah, that¡¯s because George and I have
finished our work, haven¡¯t we George?
We¡¯ve all finished
our work, so let¡¯s all play!